前情回顾...
Previously on Power...
幽灵! 我们需要谈谈
Ghost! We need to talk.
这家夜店是我的梦想
This club is the dream.
我就不认识什么满脸皱纹的老毒枭
I don't know any old, wrinkled drug dealers.
他们不是死了就是被关进去了
They're either dead or inside.
那是因为他们都没你厉害
They're not as good as you.
自从我们把尸体肢解分别送到城里
Retail side's been locked up tight
零售商就关门了
since we sent those body parts around town.
你雇了这个混蛋来偷我东西?
You hire this motherfucker to boost my product?
当然不是 我从来没见过他
Fuck, no, I've never seen him before.
阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯
他是鲁伊斯的人? 他是洛沃斯的人?
要不要送你回家?
You want a ride home?
你上次和妹子约会是什么时候啊?
When was the last time you asked a girl out on a real date?
你到底知不知道怎么约?
Do you even know how?
我上司告诉我不要分心
My boss told me not to get distracted.
但不知为何 一扯上你...
But somehow when it comes to you...
有我在
I got you.
格雷格:
我可以过来吗?
安琪:
不行 我今天要早睡
我才不会相信阿尼巴尔说的鬼话呢
I don't give a fuck what Anibal said.
他就是幕后主谋
He's behind these hits.
现在零售业务是我们的全部
Right now the retail business is all we got running.
我们都知道只靠这个挣钱入不敷出
We both know that shit alone is not paying the bills.
我们应该给阿尼巴尔点颜色看看
We need to light Anibal's ass up
以彼之道还施彼身
and turn this fucking tap back on.
阿尼巴尔一直是一个
Anibal has always been a person
安于现状的人
who likes the status quo.
我没有见他做过像那样的事
I don't see him making a move like that.
他实在是太懒了
He's too fucking lazy.
只有一种可能 有人布局
It's just as possible somebody's setting him up.
老大 你总是想太多
You over-think everything, man.
我们把那兔崽子烤得屁滚尿流
We burnt the shit out of that kid,
然后他告诉我们这是肥仔让他干的
and he told us that fatboy gave him the job.
我觉得事情就是这样
Case closed for me.
如果是卡南的话早就干掉这个混蛋了
Kanan would've had this motherfucker toe up already.
对 但我不是他妈的卡南
Yeah, and I ain't fucking Kanan.
我们已经按兵不动好几天了
We're having this sit-down in a couple of days.
我们再等等 不给他们提供货源
We kept 'em all dry for a minute now.
那么那个不着急的混蛋
The motherfucker who ain't thirsty
就是袭击我们的人
is the one hitting us.
当我们面对面盯着他们的眼睛
We'll know for sure who's behind this shit
就能确定谁是幕后主谋
when we're across a table staring them all in the eye.
如果那人不在他们之中呢?
What if it ain't one of them?
我的意思是...
I mean...
你有没有想过洛沃斯才是这一切的幕后主谋?
you ever think Lobos might be the one behind all this shit?
我他妈每天都在想
Every damn day.
但是我猜不透他为什么这么做
But I can't figure out why he'd do it,
他想整我们的话不费吹灰之力
why he wouldn't have had us capped already.
所以在我找出这些逼事的合理答案之前
So until I got good answers to those fucking questions,
我得假设他没有参与
I gotta assume Lobos ain't involved.
我们会后交流下意见
We'll compare notes after this meeting
- 然后再看怎么算账 - 好的
- and see where we end up. - All right.
我们要找出是谁和我们对着干
We're gonna find out who's fucking with us.
然后杀了他们
And then we're gonna kill 'em.
那不是我的宝贝女儿吗! 嘿 过来!
There's my baby girl! Hey, come here!
哟 近来如何 "T"?
Yo, what's up, "T"?
- 去和汤米叔叔打个招呼 - 来这里
- Go say hey to Uncle Tommy. - Come here.
你去哪啦?
Where you been?
和凯莎出去了
Out... with 'Keisha.
- 凯莎 - 怎么啦?
- Keisha. - What?
别管她 你知道她是我的朋友
Leave her alone. You know that's my friend.
嗯哼 你的朋友总是
Mm-hmm, your friend that has everything
说东道西
to say about everything.
对了 你们自从那晚的事之后都很小心?
Yas doing all right after that thing the other night?
对 差点都忘了 当然
Yas has forgotten about it, of course.
始终在我脑海挥之不去
I can't get it out of my head.
她前一秒还是好好的 突然就出事了 对吗?
She was just fine, and then, boom. Yeah?
人生就是这样
That's how things happen.
生命瞬息万变
Your whole life can change in one breath.
我还是想不通
I'm still trying to figure out
在她身边怎么会有钥匙圈
where she got the keychain from in the first place.
我得和保姆好好谈谈
You know, I'm gonna talk to the housekeeper about it.
- 现在已经不重要了 不是吗? - 对
- It don't matter now, right? - Right.
珍惜我们现在拥有的
Count our blessings while we have 'em.
嘿! 辛西娅来商谈关于莎顿庄园派对的事了
Hey! Cynthia's here to talk about the Sutton Place Party.
- 很好 她在哪? - 就在你办公室
- Cool, where is she? - She's in your office.
别做亏本生意 好吗?
Now don't give away the store to get this party, all right?
给她个好价码 但也别让利太多
Offer her a good deal, not a great one.
- 嗯 - 需要我陪你吗?
- Mm. - Should I come with?
我自己来
I got this.
我定好了意大利场子
I got us 8:00 reservations at that Italian spot
在七号八点
at 7th and the Park.
在你的生活中一定很少有人拒绝你
You haven't heard the word "No" very often in your life,
没错吧?
have you?
我常常被拒绝 只是无视它而已
I hear it all the time, I just ignore it.
你得再找一天了
You have to find another date.
或许会有些姑娘从猎豹车换班
Maybe there's some girls getting off their shift at Cheetah's.
嘿 告诉坎托斯你不舒服 那我们就能出去了
Hey, tell Kantos you feel sick so we can break out.
我在工作呢
I'm working.
周四是我们最忙的一晚之一
And Thursday's one of our busiest nights.
就算你是德瑞克・基特我也没兴趣
So I don't care if you're Derek Jeter,
我才不会为了任何人而放弃一千美金的小费呢
I'm not losing out on $1,000 worth of tips for anyone.
给
Here.
这里是两千
Here's 2,000.
走吧
Let's bounce.
我不会和你做爱
I'm not gonna fuck you.
知道了 我们能走了吗?
Good to know. Can we go now?
我好像感冒了
I think I'm coming down with the flu.
那晚吸毒过量的事
That drug overdose the other night
不是你想曝光的事 詹姆斯
is not the kind of publicity you want, James.
那不是吸毒过量
It wasn't an overdose.
不过是一个姑娘吸了劣质可卡因
A girl got some bad coke.
这在哪都可能发生
Could happen anywhere.
但是在这儿发生了啊
But it happened here.
我们不太可能
And it's unseemly of us to partner with a venue
与一个因为毒品而名声在外的场地合作
that has a reputation for drug use.
一个意外还算正常
Now one incident's an anomaly,
再来一个 那么...
another one, well...
你应该知道莎顿庄园派对的预算
You should know that my budget for the Sutton Place Party
已经被大幅削减了
has been dramatically trimmed.
但你不应该把重点放在钱上
But you shouldn't focus on money.
如果我在这里做了活动...
If I have the event here...
你们就会出现在各大主流媒体上
Truth will be in every major publication
从纽约时报到中国日报
from the New York Times to China Daily.
对于像你们这样的新酒吧
That's game-changing publicity
这将是一个绝对利好的曝光机会
for a new club like yours.
你需要这次派对 相信我
You need this party, trust me.
一个派对
One party.
这次特例
It's an anomaly.
好吧 你可以用这个场地
Okay, you can have the venue.
你只需要付成本价
All you have to cover is bar and staff.
但是我要今年你剩下的聚会...
But I want the rest of your parties this year...
翠贝卡电影节 时装周 热表
Tribeca Film, Fashion Week, Hot List.
我全都要
I want them all.
好啊 不过可惜了
Okay, unfortunately
那些剩下的聚会已经被预定了
those parties are already spoken for.
时装周在帕利
Fashion Week is at Parley.
翠贝卡电影节是在威宝的
Tribeca Film Festival is at Verbatim.
西蒙・斯特恩的夜总会
Simon Stern's clubs.
我给你一个比他更好的价码
I'm offering you a better deal than he will.
正如你所说的 你的预算已经"大幅削减"了
As you said, your budget's been "Dramatically Trimmed."
安琪:
我们能见个面吗?
Can we meet up?
为什么不回去问问你的老板
Why don't you go talk to your employers
然后再来找我?
and get back to me?
我就是这样的人
That's the kind of person I am.
我做事不会先想 就做我想做的
I don't think first, I just do what I want.
你呢? 你是什么样的人?
What about you? What kind of person are you?
- 我是什么样的人? - 对啊
- What kind of person am I? - Yeah.
我不知道啊 一个普通人?
I don't know, a regular person?
你有什么爱好吗?
Do you have any hobbies?
我是说 你平时业余时间玩什么?
I mean, like, what do you for fun?
我不知道 电子游戏吧?
I don't know. Video games?
你几岁啦? 十三岁吗?
What are you, 13?
- 嘿 我们去喝一杯吧 - 吃晚饭如何?
- Hey, let's grab a drink. - What about dinner?
先喝酒再吃饭
Drink now, eat later.
记住 不要让人在软长凳上跳舞
Remember, no one dances on the banquettes.
上周那个金发婊子
That blonde bitch last week
花了我们八百美金来修复
cost us 800 bucks in refinishing
就因为她穿了双操蛋的鲁布托高跟鞋
because of her fucking Louboutins.
- 有新进展 - 辛西娅那搞定了吗?
- Headed uptown. - How'd it go with Cynthia?
嗯 我告诉她
Well, I told her all she'd have to do
如果她给我们今年剩下的所有派对
is cover bar and staff if she'd give us
她就只需要付成本价
the rest of her parties this year.
- 老大 - 你听我说
- Boss. - No, look.
我知道我们会亏点钱
I know we'll lose money.
但是你想想 如果我们有了这些项目
But hey, if we get those events, fools will be
客人们将蜂拥于此
cutting blank checks to get up in here.
我能理解你是为将来长期做打算
Look, I get that you're building for tomorrow,
但我们现在也要保持运作啊
but we gotta keep the lights on today.
目光短浅只能带来短期利益
See, short-term thinking creates short-term results.
别这样
Come on.
我六年级的第一天
My first day of sixth grade,
我找了个附近区域最壮的小孩
I find the biggest kid in P.S. 142
然后砰地一声
and bam!
我让他一屁股坐在地上了 关着灯
I put him on his ass. Lights out.
他右手还捂着下巴
Right hand to the motherfucking jaw.
之后就没有人找你麻烦了吗?
So no one ever messed with you after that?
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
二十个街区之内 我是唯一一个白人小孩
I was the only white kid for 20 blocks.
每天都挨揍
I got my ass kicked every day.
但我从没放弃
But I never gave up.
从没停止反击
I never stopped fighting.
那些人自找的
Some people are asking for it.
哇 你戴着它太美了
Wow, it looks... looks good on you.
谁戴着都会好看的
It would look good on anyone.
不是的
Not like this.
我们错过了十八年
We went 18 years,
现在感觉连两天都不想错过
now I feel like I can't even make it two days.
是啊 我懂
Yeah, I know.
我也需要见你
I needed to see you too.
这... 你为什么
This... why did you...
我只是想 给你点好的东西
I just wanted, you know, to give you something nice.
让你觉得 自己是特别的
Make you feel special.
当你看着我的时候 我就感觉自己是特别的
I feel special when you look at me.
你不需要给我买东西
You don't need to buy me anything.
所以
So...
现在是什么情况?
what now?
我们在约会吗? 是该这么叫吗?
Are we "Going out"? Is that what we called it?
我小女儿两天前差点死了 安琪
My baby daughter almost died two days ago, Angie.
你... 你有个女儿
You... you have a daughter?
我有三个孩子
I have three kids.
还有一个妻子
And I have a wife.
我差点失去了小女儿 亚斯明
I almost lost my baby girl Yasmine.
哦 亚斯明
Yasmine.
这让我想到你
And it made me think about you...
还有 我们
and us.
我没有借口 应该早点告诉你的
I got no excuse. I should've told you.
我从未停止过想你
I never stopped thinking about you...
这么多年来
all these years.
我不能要求你...
I can't just ask you...
我有一个男朋友
I have a boyfriend.
他叫格雷格
Greg.
哦 格雷格
大概我们都在自欺其人
I guess we were just fooling ourselves.
我没有告诉你格雷格的事
I didn't tell you about Greg
跟你没告诉我的理由一样
for the same reason you didn't tell me.
我只是认为...
I just thought that...
是啊 我也是
Yeah, me too.
- 你应该拿着这个 - 不
- You should take this. - No.
你不能把它还回来
You can't give it back.
那是礼物
That's a gift.
你当年离开我的时候
When you walked out of my life,
还有十天就是你的生日了
you left ten days before your birthday.
当做是一个迟到的生日礼物吧
Consider it a belated birthday present.
我应该回家了
I should go home.
你也应该去你家人身边了
You should get back to your family.
晚安 杰米
Good night, Jamie.
晚安... 安琪
Good night... Angie.
我的身体是我的私人财产
My body is my business.
好... 这财产真是酷毙了
Well... business is dope.
你妈逼
Motherfucker!
好 打他
Yeah! Beat his ass!
你他妈想要碰她?
You wanna fucking touch her?
干得好 混蛋
Yeah, yeah, fucker!
废物
Punk!
- 有种别回来 - 天啊
- Don't come back! - Jesus.
- 加油 - 快滚出去
- Yeah, come on! - Fucking get out of here!
他摸了她的屁股
Yo! He touched her ass, yo!
他罪有应得 回你该死的酒吧去
He got what he deserved. Get back in your fucking bar.
我会打倒每一个这里的混蛋
I'll beat down every motherfucker in there!
真是太棒了
That was awesome.
你他妈在说什么?
What the fuck you talking about?
我从他脖子上拽下来的
I snatched it from his neck.
这是你住的地方?
This is where you live?
我不经常在这里呆着
I don't actually spend a whole lot of time here, I guess.
我经常在外面晃悠
I kinda hang out all over.
- 和其他女孩? - 不 不是
- With other girls? - Naw! It's not like that.
- 我... - 嘘
- I just... - Shh.
我不介意
I don't care.
我之前骗了你
I lied to you before.
其实我今晚要上你了
Turns out I am gonna fuck you tonight.
我原谅你对我说谎
I forgive you for lying.
如果你骗我 我是不会原谅你的 知道吗?
If you lie to me, I won't forgive you, okay?
所以别骗我
So don't do it.
- 啊 - 好吗?
- Ah. - Okay?
- 是 - 你保证?
- Yeah. - Promise?
是
Yeah.
有毒品吗?
Got any blow?
吸着毒品做更棒
It's always better with.
是 有
Yeah. I got some.
你要休息多久才能来下一轮
How long until you can go again?
宝贝 我不知道
Girl, I don't know.
自从孩子那事儿之后
Things got better between us for a minute
- 我们的关系暂时缓和多了 - 对呀
- after the thing with the baby... - Right.
但他还是有什么事情瞒着我
but he's still keeping shit from me.
他以前从来没这样过
He's never done that before.
如果他不时常像傻瓜一样
Well, if he didn't act the fool every now and then,
他就不是男人了
then he wouldn't be a man.
哦 宝贝 看看这些
Ooh, girl, look at these.
这些是拉链的
These are fly.
我上周买了一双黑的
I bought them in black last week.
是嘛
Of course you did.
你为什么要死死跟着我呢
Is there a reason why you pressing up on me?
我的工作就是保护你
Well, it's my job to protect you.
谁告诉你我需要保护的? 幽灵吗?
Who told you I need protection? Ghost?
- 不 我只是 - 你得退后 肖恩
- No, I... I was just... - You need to back up, Shawn.
宝贝儿 你可以随时来保护我呀
Oh, well, you can protect me anytime, baby.
走吧 凯莎
Come along, 'Keisha.
放松 宝贝
Relax, girl.
众所周知 男孩子都会看上你
Everybody know that boy only got eyes for you,
都能拉两火车皮
jump in front of the damn two train for you.
你一大早就出去啦
You go out earlier this morning?
我都想你了
I missed you.
被想念的感觉不错
It's nice to be missed.
出去和凯莎逛街
I was out shopping with 'Keisha,
肖恩死死盯着我
Shawn was breathing down my neck.
我问他 他说他是保护我的
I checked him, and he said he was there to protect me.
你是不是有情况 幽灵?
Something I need to know about, Ghost?
需要我和孩子们去外地回避吗?
Me and the kids need to get out of town for a while?
不 没有的事
Nah, nothing like that.
那孩子只是保护过度了
Kid is just being over-protective,
对他的工作太认真
taking his job too seriously.
我会告诉他放轻松
I'll tell him to ease up.
下班再和你聊
I'll talk to you after work.
你去见汤米吗
You meeting up with Tommy?
去夜总会
Headed to the club.
咱们开洗衣店那时
I don't recall you getting up at the crack of dawn
我怎么不记得你天刚亮就去
to head out to the Wash N' Folds,
烘干机一天恨不得清空四次
emptying quarters out the dryer.
这不一样
This is different.
可不是嘛
Yeah, looks that way.
我还在找原因
Steady trying to figure out why.
我告诉你原因了
I told you why.
你似乎可以
Seems like you could spend the day
跟我和小亚斯在家呆着
at home with me and Yas.
像你以前那样
You know, like you used to.
我所做的每一件事都是为了你 塔莎
Everything I'm doing, I'm doing for you, Tasha!
你他妈的什么意思?
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
所有的一切
Everything.
洛沃斯纽约的分销商要和他的网点会面
So Lobos' New York distributor is meeting with his network.
我们不知道是什么时候 在哪里
We just don't know where or when it's happening.
我的线人正在帮我打探详细信息
My C.I. is trying to get me specifics,
但现在我手上没有任何消息
but as of right now I don't have anything
除了我刚才已经告诉你的
beyond what I told you already.
你线人的消息是捏造的
Your C.I.'s info is bogus.
慎重申明 我们没有听说过
For the record, we haven't heard shit
与洛沃斯纽约地区分销商有关的会议
about a big meeting with Lobos' New York distributor,
然后我们还在这满城散布消息
and we've been shaking trees all over town.
或许是你在造谣
Maybe you're shaking around trees.
或许这个导线根本就是胡说八道
Or maybe this lead is just bullshit.
不是胡说八道
It's not bullshit.
只是一个秘密调查者营造的
It's legit intel that's been cultivated
合法平台
from a confidential informant.
真正查案就是这么干的
It's how a real investigation is conducted.
轮不到你来教我
I don't need you to tell me
该怎么查案
how an investigation is conducted.
我在调查洛沃斯的时候
I been on Lobos since you were sucking
你 诺克斯 还在吃奶呢
on your mommy's titty, Knox.
我昨晚舔了你妈咪的奶子
I was on your mama's titty last night.
刚说那个胖子 说到哪儿了?
Where are we on fatman?
我们不会改变决定
Our opinion hasn't changed.
如果洛沃斯急于转换现在交际圈
If in fact Lobos is looking to switch up his current connect,
阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯会是最佳人选
Anibal Santalises would be the most likely candidate.
他有基础设施 人脉神通
He's got the infrastructure, the relationships,
又有意向
and the disposition.
我们无时无刻不在盯着他
We've got guys on him 24/7.
你们两个跟着他
I want you two on him.
如果他就是你口中的话事人
If he's the player you say he is,
我会让麦迪纳特工亲自盯梢
I want Agent Medina to handle surveillance personally.
- 萨克斯 许可就交给你了 - 明白
- Saxe, you work up the warrant. - Understood.
你接着跟分销商会议
You stay on this distributor meeting.
要是开始了 我们得在场
If it's happening, we need to be there.
鲁伊斯不会接近黑人住宅区
Ruiz won't go near Harlem.
罗拉不会去布朗克斯区
Rolla won't fuck with the Bronx,
阿尼巴尔哪个都不想去
Anibal ain't feeling either of them.
得找一个中立的地方
We need to find some neutral ground
来举行这次会面
for this sit-down.
幽灵! 明天就要干这鬼事!
Ghost! This shit's tomorrow!
我们需要一切就位
We need to get everything in place.
好 我们就在市中心的唐人街动手
Yeah, we'll do it at the Chinese spot downtown.
落星饭店? 那吃啥?
Lok Sing? What about food?
罗拉现在在搞什么食素
Rolla's on some vegan shit now.
这可不是酒席!
This ain't no goddamn catered affair!
不管我给他们上什么 汤米
I put fucking food on their table every fucking day, Tommy.
龟儿子们总得吃饭
Motherfuckers gotta eat.
如果这些人中有幕后黑手
If one of these guys is behind these hits,
得确保不能让他们先发制人
we need to make sure they don't have the drop on us.
我可不想自己人还没到齐
I don't want anybody stashing fucking gats
那边就埋伏好了 明白吗?
before we all get there, all right?
提前二十分钟过去安排好
We do it okeydoke 20 minutes before game time.
清理房间
And get the room swept.
我可不想让别人听到我们的事
I don't want anybody listening in on our shit.
我们要做就得做到底
We need to get to the bottom of this
这样事态才会恢复正常
so things will go back to normal.
这劳什子可要顺利
We need our shit to work smoothly
然后我们就能考虑其他事了
so we can think about other things.
其他什么事?
What other things?
不是这事
Not this.
你确定你父亲说在那边开会?
是的 隔着门我也能听见他打电话
真棒 给我发张自拍照吧
你先发
有什么消息?
What do you got?
你想要的消息
I got what you want.
不过你得付钱
But it's gonna cost you.
我刚在看联邦调查局的档案
I was watching the FBI files...
上面写着...
and they said...
线人是要给钱的
informants get paid.
那么...你想要这次会议的信息...
So... you want information about this meeting...
先掏钱
you pay.
我感觉到...
Something tells me...
你并不缺钱
you're not hurting for cash.
被你发现了 妈咪
You got me there, mami.
想过没有 如果我们换一种方式见面...
You ever think, if we'd met a different way...
不行
Nope.
快说我需要知道的事
Just tell me what I need to know.
明天两点 在市中心落星饭店
Lok Sing Restaurant, downtown, 2:00 tomorrow.
纽约方面也会去吗?
And the New York connect's gonna be there?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
你得带着电话
We need you to wear a wire.
我说过没人邀请我
I told you I'm not invited.
我不在内部
I'm on the outside.
那你是怎么知道的?
Then how'd you find out?
小小鸟告诉我的哟
Little birdie told me.
别招惹伊莎贝尔 诺马
Leave Isabel alone, Nomar.
如果那样你怎么能得到你那宝贵情报?
Even if that's how you get your precious information?
出去的时候小心 别让人看见你
Be careful no one makes you coming out of here.
五香烟熏牛肉 腌菜 瑞士卷 热的
Pastrami, pickles, and Swiss. Hot.
多谢把塔里克从实践课接回来
Thanks for picking up Tariq from practice.
本来是想请肖恩去的 可...
I would've asked Shawn, but...
他和幽灵在一块
he's with Ghost.
说到肖恩
Speaking of Shawn,
今天早上他可是离我相当之近
he was hanging real close this morning.
嘴上说是要保护我
Told me it was for my protection.
发生什么事了 汤米?
What's going on, Tommy?
我要考虑孩子们的
You know, I got kids to think about.
我们对付得了 别担心
We got it under control. Don't worry.
幽灵什么也不跟我说
Ghost ain't telling me shit.
他就满口都是夜总会的事
It's all, "The club this, the club that."
关于真相酒吧那些破事我真听烦了
So sick and tired of hearing about fucking Truth.
我也是!
Me too!
幽灵有没有跟你说过他从我们自己的
Did Ghost tell you he took a grip of money
账户里取了一笔钱 用到真相开张上?
out of our personal account and used it to open Truth?
这事不归我管
That's none of my business.
他甚至没跟我说一声
He didn't even tell me about it.
还是我自己发现的
I had to find out myself.
看看你家 塔莎 看看你的生活
Look where you live, Tasha. Look at your life.
在我看来
From where I'm sitting,
你的条件是相当不错的
it looks like things are playing out pretty good for you.
所以他拿了一点钱投到夜总会上这种蠢事
So he dug in a little deep on this club bullshit.
那又怎样? 改变不了你的生活
So what? Doesn't change shit about your life.
他就在改变 汤米 幽灵在变化
He's changing, Tommy. Ghost is changing.
对我们两个都不好
And that's not good for either of us.
还有没有熏牛肉了?
You got any more pastrami up in here?
你真该乘"B" 换到"N" 或者 "R"
You should really take the "B" to the "N" or the "R"
从安全房出来就是
from the safe house.
你跟踪我?
You tailed me?
你要是坚持自己看看这件破事
If you insist on seeing that piece of shit alone,
我会护你周全
I'm gonna watch your back.
你不能就这么监视我 格雷格
You can't fucking spy on me, Greg.
你说的是
You're right.
我应该告诉弗兰基 你在破坏协定
Instead I should tell Frankie that you're subverting protocol
跟那个笨蛋调情
to play footsie with that dick.
他给你什么了吗?
Did he even give you anything?
我拿到地址了
I got the address.
你真厉害
You're good.
你居然跟踪我
You're fucking stalking me.
我跟踪你...
I'm only stalking you...
只是因为我太喜欢你了
because I like you so much.
你是个傻蛋
You're a dumbass.
你就是我这傻蛋的软肋
You're a pain in my dumb ass.
你有没有跟弗兰基说诺马的话?
Did you tell Frankie about what Nomar said?
- 她会把装甲部队都叫来的 - 我知道
- She's gonna call in the cavalry. - I know.
- 最好直接去 - 我知道
- Better go right. - I know that.
你觉得
What do you think
我在这儿留几件衣服怎么样?
about me leaving some clothes over here?
我是说我每周得在这儿住几晚上
At this point, I'm staying over here a few nights a week.
对我来说留些东西会方便些
It'll be easier for me to just leave some shit here.
抽屉里还有地方吗?
You got any room in this drawer?
那到底是什么?
What the hell was that?
安吉拉 里面究竟是什么?
Angela, what the hell was that?
你在抽屉里藏了什么吗?
Are you hiding something in that drawer?
- 当然没有 - 那你在搞什么?
- Of course not. - Then what's the problem?
怎么了?
What's going on here?
你不想出去约会
You haven't wanted to hang out,
我们真出去的时候又心不在焉
you've been distracted when we have hung out,
现在我说想留几件衣服在这儿
and now you practically take my hand off
你其实又不让我这么做
when I mentioned leaving some clothes over here.
出了什么事?
So what's up?
我们在这里干什么?
I mean, what are we doing here?
你是不是看上别人了?
Is there someone else?
没有
No.
我没看上谁
There's no one else.
那是怎么了?
Then what is it?
我要回家了
I'm going home.
格雷格!
Greg!
街上有监控
We have directional cameras set up on the street,
但是我们看不到里面
but we couldn't get inside.
在过去的一天里
There's just too many people going in and out of there
来来往往的人很多
over the past 24 hours.
你们听到了吗? 我们看不到里面
Did you guys hear that? We couldn't get inside.
控制 分配
Control, dispatch, for a 730 switching,
再次重复 准备行动
secondary transmission. Stand by.
据巴尔德斯说
According to Valdes,
会议在一个小时后开始
this meeting's supposed to start in an hour.
是的 不过阿尼巴尔还在他的家里
Yeah, and Anibal's still up in his house
吃樱桃加西亚冰淇淋
eating pints of Cherry fucking Garcia.
他缺席 这场会议如何进行?
How the hell are they gonna have a meeting without him?
这里根本没有会议
That's because there is no meeting.
巴尔德斯满嘴跑火车
Valdes is full of shit.
你更想和谁上床? 巴尔德斯还是弗兰基?
Who'd you rather bang, Valdes or Frankie?
- 弗兰基不和男人上床 - 我知道!
- Frankie don't take dick. - I know!
我们只是假设
But let's just say she does.
或者她真的会
Or she would.
我会和弗兰基上床
I'd go with Frankie.
我喜欢波霸
I like a broad with balls.
啊 我想我会和巴尔德斯上床
Ah, I think I'd smash Valdes.
她的脸上总是表现得
She's always got that expression on her face
好像她能满足她自己
like she's so fucking full of herself.
我想要看到当我上她时
I wanna see what her face looks like
她脸上的表情
when she's full of me.
应该是半饱
You mean half full.
混蛋
Fuck you.
他们都在路上了
They're all on their way.
正是时候
Time for the okeydoke.
我们也去吧
Do it now.
你总是脚踏实地是吗? 坎托斯
You always land on your feet, don't you, Kantos?
主管是谁
Who's the man in charge?
近在眼前
You're looking at him.
没有人蠢到为你提供资金 坎托斯
Nobody is stupid enough to bankroll a spot for you, Kantos.
得了吧 老板在哪?
Come on. Where's the boss?
他不在
He's not here.
- 我能帮上什么忙? - 什么都不能
- What can I help you with? - Jack shit.
你真的什么都帮不了我们
You can help us with exactly jack shit.
我们需要马上见到你的老板
We need to be laying eyes on your boss right now,
否则你今晚或以后
or you're not gonna be opening up your doors tonight
都别想营业了
or any other night.
我找了维克多 达里恩 奶酪和杰斯基
I got Victor, Darien, Queso, and Jayski
让他们在门口拍身搜查那些龟儿子们带的武器
patting motherfuckers down for steel at the door.
至于食品
Now as far as food goes, I'm just having them bring
我让他们给每个人送上一个
those fucking Pu Pu platter joints with a little
装满了各式各样东西的宝宝盘
something-something for everybody.
我估计阿尼巴尔那个贱人一定会饿的
I figure Anibal's gonna be hungry as a motherfucker.
你记得他吃过二十五个甜甜圈吗?
You remember when he ate 25 donuts?
喂?
Yeah?
让我们关门? 今晚?
Shutting us down? Tonight?
我在路上 坎托斯
I'm on my way, Kantos.
送我去夜总会
Drop me off at the club.
你去那干嘛?
Where the fuck you going?
警察说要跟我当面谈一谈
Cops saying they're gonna shut down Truth
否则他们就关了真相夜总会
unless they speak to me face to face.
你得自己去参加会议了 兄弟
You're gonna have to run this meeting solo, Bro.
你不跟我一起了?
Are you fucking with me?
我们被盯上了 你关了它吧
We're getting hit, you shut shit down.
现在我们有一个全集团会议
Now we got an entire network meeting
但是你却要去处理夜总会的破事?
and you're gonna go deal with some bullshit at the club?
他们要关了夜总会 汤米!
They're shutting the club down, Tommy!
我们在这里洗白的钱
We wash more money up in there than we do
比其他任何地方都多
at every other front we got combined.
你想让我就这么关门了?
You want me to just fuck this off?
- 正是如此 - 他们要见老板
- Hell, yeah, I do. - They want the fucking owner.
老板是我 我要去处理
That's me. I gotta deal with it.
你自己能应对 汤米
You can handle this on your own, Tommy.
我可不信
I don't even believe this shit.
你记住了
You got this.
别告诉他们你回心转意了
Just don't tell them you're turning shit back on.
不揪出是谁在捣鬼
Until we know who's hitting us,
我们就不供货
we're not moving any weight.
- 去找胡里奥 - 没时间了
- Go get Julio. - No time.
我带这小子跟我一起
I'll take the kid with me.
你做完了之后通知我
Hit me when you're done.
准备好今天掉脑袋了吗? 小子
You ready for your balls to drop today, kid?
我要这栋楼所有人的照片
I want photos of anybody and everybody on that block.
我才不在乎小萨莉・金博尔
I don't give a shit if it's little Sally Kimball
是否在溜她的狮子狗
walking her cockapoo,
我要她的照片和身份证
I want her photographed and I.D.'d,
以及狗的证件号码
and I want the dog's license number.
所有的照相机都准备好了吗?
Are all our cameras up?
准备好了
They're up.
6987 再次确认
6987, now confirmed to copy.
出发
Out.
有人看见我的运动鞋了吗?
所有东西都有许可
Everything's been permitted,
这地方符合规定 我们所有的执照...
the place is up to code, all our licenses...
生意 饮料 噪音... 都是合法的
business, beverage, noise... are current.
要知道 问题是... 吉米...
Yeah, you see, the problem is, Jimmy...
你不介意我叫你"吉米"吧?
you don't mind if I call you "Jimmy," do you?
要知道 问题是我们知道这个公司
See, the problem is we know illegal narcotics
出售非法的麻醉药
have been sold inside this establishment.
如你所想 这对我们来说是一个大问题
As you can imagine that's a big problem for us.
是的 我们现在正在追查
Yeah, well, we're in the process
那个卖家
of tracking down the dealer right now.
我保证 只要我找到他
And I'm gonna make sure I turn him over to you
就会把他移交给你 好吗? 我向你保证
as soon as I find him, okay? You have my word.
这真棒 吉米
And that's great, Jimmy.
我的意思是 每个男人都会对他的话负责
I mean, that's all a man really has, right?
对吗?
His word.
但是在这种情况下 我认为
But in this instance, I don't think your word's
你没有说假话
really gonna do the trick.
所以你怎么想的 艾德 两周左右?
So what are you thinking, Ed, two weeks or so?
我不太明白 你的"两周"是什么意思?
I'm not following. What do you mean by "Two Weeks"?
吉米 我们要让你
Jimmy, we gotta shut you down
至少停业14天
for at least 14 business days.
这完全没有理由 我们要做生意
This is totally unreasonable. We have a business to run.
我们要检查你的所有文件
We gotta go through all your paperwork,
我们要检查卫生和防火措施
we gotta get health in here, we gotta get fire in here.
我们要确认所有的事情都是正大光明的
We gotta make sure everything's on the up and up.
长官 我已经告诉你了
Officer, I just told you.
每件事都是合乎规定的
Everything's up to code.
有时候事情看起来的
Well, sometimes it seems that way
与它实际的样子完全相反
when it really isn't that way.
一派胡言!
This is bullshit!
够了 这样
Enough. Look.
给我和我的同伴一点时间解决问题
What do you say you give my partner and I some time, huh,
怎么样?
to work out the kinks?
- 非常乐意 - 这是我的荣幸
- Pleasure. - The pleasure's mine.
哦 嘿
Oh, and hey...
记得通知我们麻醉药的消息
keep us posted on that drug sting of yours.
- 他们会回来的 - 当然会
- They're gonna be back. - No shit.
- 这是一个饭店? - 是的
- This is a restaurant? - Yeah.
做我们这行的 最好不要走前门
In our business, you try not to use the front door.
哦 嘿 嘿 嘿 抱歉
Oh, hey, hey, hey. Sorry.
一会儿要这么做
Here's how it's gonna play.
我坐着 你站在我身后
I sit down, you stand behind me.
直视前方
Look straight ahead.
你不要看任何人的眼睛
You don't look anyone in the eye.
无论如何 一个字也别说
And no matter what, you don't say a fucking word.
绝不
Ever.
顺便说一下 我想了很久了
And by the way, while I'm thinking of it,
别管塔莎了 伙计
lay off Tasha, man.
无论什么情况下都别疑神疑鬼的吓着她
You don't spook her under any circumstances.
懂了吗? 让幽灵管好他老婆
Get it? Let Ghost handle his wife.
好了 是时候把注意力放在会谈上了
All right, time to focus on this sit-down.
别打扰我 伙计
Stop distracting me, man.
这是什么?
What the fuck?
这是怎么回事?
What is it?
这不是什么好东西
It ain't anything good.
伊丽莎白大街的入口怎么样 发生了什么?
What about the entrance on Elizabeth Street, anything?
一切正常
Nothing.
有别的入口吗?
Is there another way in?
等下
Wait.
这些建筑下面
Isn't there an old tunnel system
有没有铺管队用过的
underneath all these buildings
老隧道系统?
that the Tongs used back in the day?
是的
Yeah.
但是在多耶斯大街有个入口
But the entrance to the only remaining tunnel
通向仅剩的隧道
is on Doyers Street.
出口在且林士果广场
That's out on Chatham Square.
他们不会走这个隧道过来
They wouldn't use that to come here.
我只是在想这附近的地下有什么
I'm just thinking about what's underneath this neighborhood.
给我一张饭店的设计图
Get me a blueprint for the restaurant.
安吉拉 特工们已经详细检查过那栋大楼了
Angela, the agents already canvassed the building.
所有入口都已经
The entrances are covered.
他们翻遍每一层楼了吗?
Did they walk through all the floors?
你看看 从街上没有其他入口可以进入落星
See, there's no other entrance to Lok Sing from the street.
但是如果他们从后面的大楼进入
But if they came from the building behind it,
地下室还有一个连接门可以进入
the basement could still have a connecting door underground.
仅从街面上看 你不会知道
Street level, you'd never know
还可以那样子进入餐厅
you could get to the restaurant that way.
我们早该猜到
We should have known.
他们这么狡猾 不会从正门进入的
They're too smart to walk through the front door.
这只是个猜测
It's a guess.
- 你说得对 - 我们再看看情况吧
- You're right. - We looked.
- 你真的确定吗? - 嗯哼
- Are you absolutely sure? - Mm-hmm.
因为这由你来下令 你需要承担责任的
Because it's your call. It's on you.
而且如果我是对的 而他们正在那儿
And if I'm right, and they're in there,
那么我们就要马上进去了
then we gotta go in right now.
我们没有他们的把柄
We don't have shit on them.
总不能因为他们在享用午餐
We can't bust in there and arrest them
就冲进去而逮捕他们
for just having lunch.
我只是想看看他的样子 格雷格
I just want to see his face, Greg.
我只是想见见他 知道他的身份
I want to see him and know who he is.
一旦我们确认发行人的身份
Once we I.D. that distributor,
我们就离揭穿他 抓到洛沃斯很近了
we're this close to turning him and getting Lobos.
我们准备进去
We're going in.
我想阿尼巴尔不会来了
I guess Anibal can't tell time.
所以...
So...
大家都怎么样了?
how's everybody doing?
如果我们有货可以卖 会做得更好
We'd be better if we had product to sell.
- 我在损失地盘 - 我也是
- I'm losing corners. - Me too.
那就是你踩过界的原因吗?
Is that why you've been stepping all over mine?
那些不是我的人
Those aren't my people.
就算他们是黑人 也不代表他们是我的人
Just 'cause they black don't make 'em mine.
- 他们打着你的旗号 - 乱讲
- They flying your flag. - Bullshit.
即使他们承认是我的人 也是在说谎
And if they say they are, they lying.
- 闭嘴 - 罗拉 你在说谎
- Shut up. - You're lying, Rolla.
鄙视你 鲁伊斯
Kiss my ass, Ruiz.
快给我闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
在街上我们可以发牢骚
We may beef on the streets,
但在这 我们是生意合作伙伴
but in here, we're business partners.
说到伙伴 你的伙伴去哪了?
Speaking of partners, where's yours?
我们召开这么重大会议
We call this big, important meeting
而幽灵根本不屑露面?
and Ghost doesn't even bother to show up?
所以他不但不给我们货...
So not only is he not getting us product...
他还不屑于来这里?
but he doesn't respect us enough to be here?
我在墨西哥有门路
I got a connect in Mexico.
说他可以帮我们找到货源
Says he can get us fish scale
仅需我们现在付出价格的一半
for half of what we're paying now.
从何而来?
Out of where?
努埃瓦・利昂
Nueva Leon.
幽灵对我们要价过高
Ghost has been overcharging us.
我们可以得到更好
We can do better.
我回心转意了
I'm turning shit back on.
我打算对在座的各位再次开始供货
I'm gonna start moving weight to all of you again.
嘿
Hey.
先让特工们搜查一下房间 安吉拉
Let the agents clear the room first, Angela.
想跟鲁伊兹去试试其他门路的
You wanna go with Ruiz and try another connect,
请便
go right ahead.
我们很高兴跟了你和幽灵  汤米
We're happy with you and Ghost, Tommy.
我们不跟西班牙人做交易
We don't do business with the Spanish.
你什么意思 西班牙人?
What do you mean, Spanish?
我看上去像是从西班牙来的吗 混蛋?
I look to you like I'm from Spain, motherfucker?
当你回来...
When you come back...
联邦调查局! 把手举到看得见的地方!
FBI! Let me see your hands!
跪着求我们因为我们的货更纯的时候
On your knees 'cause our shit is purer,
我们会收你双倍的 鲁伊斯
we're gonna charge you double, Ruiz.
别动!
Don't move!
这里的春卷跟落星的根本没法比
Spring rolls up in this spot ain't got shit on Lok Sing.
事实上 现在要能吃上落星的青豆什么的
In fact, I'd consider sucking a dick right now
让我舔他老二我都会考虑
for some of them Lok Sing green beans.
天啊 不要吧
Oh, hell, no.
为什么你在最后几秒钟
Why you switch up the spot for the meeting
要换开会的场地?
at the last second?
再小心都不为过
Can never be too careful.
要让他们猜不透
Always keep 'em guessing.
能给我拿把叉子吗?
Can I get a fork, please?
我们得知道谁在打压我们
We gotta know who's been hitting us.
阿尼巴尔到底在哪?
Where the fuck is Anibal?
多久了?
How long?
可能一到两个小时
It could be one or two hours,
不超过三个小时
three at the most.
只有脖子上的切口吗?
And it was just the cut to the neck?
就这样 看上去很专业
That's all she wrote. Looks professional.
对不起 失陪一下
Excuse me for a minute.
你到底是谁 为什么会在我的犯罪现场里?
Who are you, and why the fuck are you in my crime scene?
- 禁药取缔机构  - 滚开
- DEA. - Fuck off.
这是纽约警察的差事
This is NYPD business.
我们正因桑塔利斯
We were surveilling Santalises
涉及费利佩・洛沃斯的事而监视他
for involvement with Felipe Lobos.
你是说这案件发生时你就在外面?
You mean you were right outside when this happened?
喔
Wow.
了不起的犯罪拦截啊 先生
Bang-up criminal interdiction there, gentlemen.
我想现在开始该由我来负责
I think I'll handle it from here.
-警官... - 滚开
- Detective... - Beat it!
走吧
Let's go.
你在哪?
Where you at?
这个商谈早该结束了吧
This sit-down should've ended a while ago.
回电我
Hit me back.
什么商谈?
What sit-down?
只是想找汤米 嘿
Just trying to find Tommy. Hey.
汤米一个人去商谈?
Tommy went to a sit-down alone?
不 他把肖恩也带上了
No, he took Shawn with him.
肖恩?
Shawn?
什么时候少了你
Since when do Tommy and Shawn
汤米和肖恩也可以去开会了?
do meetings without you?
汤米得开始进步啦
Tommy needs to start stepping it up.
为什么? 你要去什么地方吗?
Why? You going somewhere?
不 我哪也不去 塔莎
No, I'm not going anywhere, Tasha.
我就在这 你想我在的地方
I'm stuck here, right where you want me.
商谈是关于什么的?
What was the sit-down about?
洛沃斯先生 近来可好?
Senor Lobos. Que paso?
肖恩 我是塔莎
Shawn, it's Tasha.
我想你帮我带一些生活用品过来
I need you to pick up some groceries for me.
幽灵 最近好吗?
Fantasma, how are you?
事情进展得如何?
How's things?
一切尽在掌握中 头儿
Things are under control, Jefe.
是吗?
Are they?
我觉得一个普利美拉成员的死
I find it interesting that
和另一个人的不服从
the death of one Primera
搭上你对"一切尽在掌握中"的定义
and the insubordination of another
真的很有趣
meet your definition of... "Under Control."
死?
Death?
阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯
泰诺人兄弟
都不复存在了
我发现你很惊讶啊
我原本希望他就是问题的根源
I was hoping he was the problem,
而你除掉了他
and you eliminated him.
但现在我知道我想错了
But now I see I was wrong.
你从哪儿听到这些?
纽约警察该给高一点的工资
NYPD should pay better.
从你们执法部门套消息真的好便宜
问题不是为什么我知道
The question is not why I know
阿尼巴尔死了
that Anibal is dead,
而是为什么你不知道
the question is why you don't know
阿尼巴尔已经死了
Anibal is dead,
并且你的朋友比沃拉・鲁伊斯
and why your friend, Vibora Ruiz,
很渴望取代你
is so anxious to take your position
在我组织里的位置
in my organization.
他直接联系你了?
He reached out to you directly?
当然
Of course.
出于维护你 我拒绝了他的提议
I said no to his proposal out of deference to you,
并且承诺你会处理
and the promise that you would handle
你关系网络中的问题
the problems in your network...
一个至今仍未实现的承诺
A promise that is yet unfulfilled.
幽灵 我无法忍受为我工作的人里
You see, Ghost, I refuse to tolerate disloyalty
有背信弃义的人
in the men that work for me.
只要我发现有不忠诚的人
The moment I detect disloyalty,
我就会像对癌症一样除之而后快
I cut it out like a cancer.
如果你不除 它就会扩散
If you don't, it will grow
然后整个器官就会坏死
and the whole organism will die.
我在处理这个状况了 头儿
那你就继续说吧
晚安 幽灵
Have a good night, Ghost.
我特别跟你说 别告诉他们
I specifically told you not to tell them
我们什么时候回心转意
when we're turning shit back on.
鲁伊斯说他另有门路 而且价格更优惠
Ruiz said he had another connect with a better price.
此次会面的全部重点
The whole point of the meeting
是要搞清楚谁在打劫我们
was to figure out who's robbing us.
你说过不急着要货的孙子
You said the motherfucker who ain't thirsty
就是袭击我们的人
is the guy who's hitting us.
阿尼巴尔来都没来
Anibal didn't even show to the meeting.
这对你来说够不着急了吧?
Is that not thirsty enough for you?
- 阿尼巴尔死了 - 别扯犊子
- Anibal's dead. - Get the fuck out of here.
洛沃斯打电话告诉我的
Lobos called and told me.
他他妈是怎么知道的?
How the fuck does he know?
- 他在纽约警察局有人 - 老天爷!
- He got people in NYPD. - Jesus Christ!
你干的吧?
You do it?
- 干什么? - 阿尼巴尔
- Do what? - Anibal.
你似乎十分肯定就是他在跟我们捣乱
You seemed pretty fucking sure it was him hitting us.
你是不是又惹祸上身了?
Are you taking shit into your own hands, huh?
- 过来 - 我就在这儿呢
- Come here to me. - I'm already here.
给我闪一边去
Get out of my face.
你他妈跟我开玩笑吗?
You fucking kidding me?
你以为是我杀了阿尼巴尔?
You think I killed Anibal?
你觉得我会那么玩弄你吗?
You think I'd play you like that?
我们谈过了
We had a conversation.
你告诉我要沉住气 我照办了
You told me sit tight, and I did.
我还告诉你别告诉他们
I also told you not to tell them
我们何时开始供货呢
we were gonna start moving shit.
我他妈没杀阿尼巴尔 幽灵
I didn't fucking kill Anibal, Ghost.
洛沃斯说鲁伊斯是幕后指使
Lobos said Ruiz is behind this shit.
说他跟他谈过要上位的事
Said he met with him about stepping it up.
他想就着这次会面脱离我们
He was gapping the fuck off as this meeting.
鲁伊斯不能留了 汤米
Ruiz has to go, Tommy.
干 对 决一死战 兄弟
Fuck, yeah. Do or die, baby.
不成功便成仁
Do or die.
菇凉 正如你所说
Girl, it's like you said.
如果我想知道幽灵想做什么
You know, if I wanna know what Ghost is up to,
还有谁能比
then who better to tell me
整天跟着他的小跟班更清楚呢?
than the cat who's with him all day?
我还不能说
I mean, I wouldn't say
他已经是我的掌中之物了
he's wrapped around my little finger yet...
但是他会的
but he will be.
你应该在Instagram应用上关注我
You should follow me on Instagram.
你应该把手拿开
You should get your hand off my ass.
对不起 安琪
- 有何感想? - 辛西娅有消息了吗?
- How we feeling? - You hear from Cynthia yet?
还没 不过别担心 老板
No. But don't worry, Boss.
- 外面排队的有一条街那么长 - 靠
- Line outside's a block long. - Damn.
嗨
Hey.
那个人 有劣质毒品的那个人
That guy, the one with the bad blow?
他在七号桌
He's at table seven.
龟儿子回来了
Son of a bitch came back.
- 要给纽约警察局打电话吗? - 不
- Should I call NYPD? - Nah.
可你跟条子们说过如果他再出现
But you told those cops we'd hit 'em up
就会报警
if he showed again.
是 我知道我跟他们说了什么
Yeah, I know what I told them.
把他搬到贵宾室 让他免费喝
Move him up to VIP, let him drink for free.
- 我不明白 - 照做就是了
- I don't get it. - Just do it.
汤米 你忙吗?
圣帕特里克夫人!
Mrs. St. Patrick!
Mrs. St. Patrick.
塔莎!
Tasha!
圣帕特里克夫人?
Mrs. St. Patrick?
我带了你想要的东西
I'm back from the store with that stuff you wanted.
圣帕特里克夫人 嗨
Mrs. St. Patrick, hey.
哇! 太棒了
Whoa! All right, yeah!
你们哪位可爱的女士想跟我来一发?
Which one of you lovely ladies wants to get on this dick?
我们要去了结了这龟儿子的快活日子
We're about to cancel Christmas on this motherfucker.
我不能留着它
I can't keep it.
我试过了...
I tried...
但我一看到它就想起你 想起我们
but I look at it and I think of you and us
以及所有一切未发生
and everything that didn't happen
不能发生也不会发生的事
and can't happen and won't happen.
我不能那样活 杰米...
I can't live my life like that, Jamie...
总想着可能会如何如何
thinking about what could've been.
我们做不了朋友
We can't be friends.
远远不够
It'll never be enough.
我得走了
I gotta go.
别这样
Don't.
我也跟你做不了朋友
I can't be friends with you either.
别再去那家夜总会了
Don't ever go back to that club.
听见了吗?
You hear me?
别做毒品生意了 蠢货
Get out the damn drug business, dummy.
你的烂货能要人命
Your shit could kill somebody.